

DANG-HUNG PHAN
PhD student -Iowa State University
(2015-2020)

\*Latest update: March, 5th, 2017.

I am second year student in Dr. Hridesh Rajan's laboratory in Computer Science Department, Iowa State University. My research focuses on apply Statistical Learning for Software Engineering problems. I mined the context of Software Corpuses, including program specifications and source code by advantages of Machine Translation system, to solved the Specification Inference, Type Inference and Code-to-Code translation. The publications related to these work is shown in [9].

### 1. PERSONAL DETAILS

Full Name Dang-Hung PHAN ("Phan Đăng Hưng" in Vietnamese)

First Name Hung
Middle Name Dang
Last Name Phan

**Current job** PhD student at Computer Science Department, Iowa State University.

Advisor(s) - Dr. Hridesh Rajan (<a href="http://web.cs.iastate.edu/~hridesh/">hridesh/</a>)

- Dr. Tien N. Nguyen (<a href="http://www.utdallas.edu/~tien.n.nguyen/">http://www.utdallas.edu/~tien.n.nguyen/</a>)

Passport ID B7560637

**Date of Birth** December 30, 1989

**Gender** Male

**Born Place** Hanoi, Viet Nam

Home Address Number 12, 908 Douglas avenue, Ames Iowa 50010, USA.

Office address 115-2 Atanasoff Hall, Iowa State University, Ames, IA, 50011

**Education level** Bachelor degree (2012).

**Language** - Vietnamese (native language)

- English (Get TOEFL score of 89, taken at November, 2013).

**Phone** 5157356030

Email <u>hungphd@iastate.edu</u>, <u>pdhung3012@gmail.com</u>

Personal page <a href="http://hungphd.public.iastate.edu/">http://hungphd.public.iastate.edu/</a>

#### 2. OBJECTIVE

- To be a good IT programmer.
- To be a good researcher.
- Try to learning as much as possible and doing my best in order to complete my task.
- To have good opportunities to get promotion in my job.
- Develop my skills with development of company, I want to prove myself in many other skills.

#### 3. EDUCATION

Year (From-to)	Studying
8/2016 - 8/2020	PhD student at Computer Science Department, Iowa State University.
7/2015- 7/2016	PhD student at Electrical and Computer Engineering Department, Iowa State University.
2007 – 2012	Studied at School Of Information & Communication Technology (SOICT)- Hanoi University Of Science And Technology (HUST). Class: Software Engineering- course 52 (SE C52)
2004 – 2007	Studied at Luong The Vinh High School- Cau Giay District, Ha Noi, Viet Nam.

#### 4. FOREIGN LANGUAGE CERTIFICATES

Month/ Year (Fromto)	Certificates
11/2013	<b>TOEFL iBT Certificate</b> : score 89 (Reading 22, Listening 21, Speaking 22, Writing 25)

### 5. INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (IT) PROGRAMING SKILLS

Topic	Related Programming languages/IT platforms
Web	HTML, PHP, JSP, ASP. NET
Database	SQL Server, Mysql, Ontology
Programming	Pascal, C/C++, Java, C#, Python
Operating System	Window, Linux- Ubuntu
	DI 1 ADG11 11 000 11 D 11 D

Other Photoshop, 3DS Max, Ms. Office, VietTagger, JVnTextPro

# 6. IT PROJECTS PARTICIPATED

Month/ year	<b>Project; Position: Programming languages</b>
5/2015-5-2017	Research Assistant at Iowa State University. IT developer: Java, C#.
8/2012- 4/2014	Took part in Vietnam State Project "The two-way machine translation system with domain oriented". IT developer: Java, ASP.NET, C#, Python, Ubuntu Linux Server, Windows Server.
7/2012- 3/2013	IT developer of the "Vietnamese News Reading Assistant" (ViNAS) system; <b>IT developer: C#, ASP.NET.</b>
1/2012- 7/2012	IT developer of the Semantic Innovation Group (SIG) research team. Guided by Dr. Cao Tuan Dung (SOICT- HUST); <b>IT developer: Java, JSF Web Application.</b>
6/2011-7/2012	Took part in the <b>BKProfile</b> project- a knowledge question-aswering system for Vietnamese (SOICT- HUST); <b>IT developer: PHP, Zend framework</b> .
6/2009-7/2011	Work as a leader and project manager of IT defenses at SOICT; <b>IT developer: C, Java, C#, PHP, ASP.NET</b> .
5-2010-8/2010	Worked at the Sunnet media company - Number 72, Truong Chinh Street, Ha Noi City; <b>IT developer: Java, PHP.</b>

# **7. IT RESEARCHES**

Topic	Related Programming languages/IT platforms
Speech processing	Text To Speech, Automatic Speech Recognition
Semantic web	Ontology building, information extractor, SPARQL, Jena
Machine learning	SVM, Decision Tree, Bayesian, Neural Network
•	

# 8. RESEARCH EXPERIENCES

Month/ year	Project; Research area
7/2014-6/ 2015	Works as researcher in Samsung Mobile R&D center- Research area: Text mining, pattern recognition.
2/2012- 6/2014	Works as a researcher in Computer Science at the Institute of Information Technology (IOIT), Vietnam Academy Science and Technology of Vietnam - Research area; Speech processing.
1/2012- 7/2012	Research and develop the VHO ontology application for history

field in the Semantic Innovation Group (SIG) research team. Guided by Dr. Cao Tuan Dung (SOICT- HUST).

### 9. PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENT

Month/ year	Achievements: Details
5/2017	International Research Publication: Statistical Learning for Inference between Implementations and Documentation.  Authors: Hung Phan, Hoan Nguyen, Tien Nguyen and Hridesh Rajan. New Ideas and Emerging Results at ICSE 2017 (http://icse2017.gatech.edu/)
5/2017 5/2017	International Research Publication: Statistical Migration of API Usages. Authors: Hung Phan, Anh Nguyen, Trong Nguyen and Tien Nguyen. Demonstration track at ICSE 2017 ( <a href="http://icse2017.gatech.edu/">http://icse2017.gatech.edu/</a> )
3/2017	International Research Publication: Exploring API Embedding for API Usages and Applications. Authors: Trong Nguyen, Anh Nguyen, Hung Phan and Tien Nguyen. Research paper at ICSE 2017 (http://icse2017.gatech.edu/)
12/2014	International Research Publication: Applying Skip-gram word estimation and SVM-based classification for opinion mining Vietnamese food places text reviews; Authors: Hung Phan and Tuan-Dung Cao; Full paper of the Fifth international symposium on information and communication technology (SOICT-2014); URL: <a href="http://www.soict.hust.edu.vn/~soict2014/index.php">http://www.soict.hust.edu.vn/~soict2014/index.php</a>
04/2014	International Research Publication: Improving prosodic information for HMM-based synthesized Vietnamese Aviation announcements; Authors: Quan Tran Lam, Dinh Anh Tuan, Hung Phan Dang; Full paper of the 1st NAFOSTED International Conference (NAFOSTED-2014); URL: <a href="http://nafosted.gov.vn/nics2014/">http://nafosted.gov.vn/nics2014/</a>
12/2013	International Research Publication: Context-aware aviation search engine; Authors: Quan Tran Lam, Hung Phan Dang; Full paper of the 5 <sup>th</sup> International Conference of Soft Computing and Pattern Recognition (SOCPAR-2013); URL:

	http://www.mirlabs.org/socpar13/
11/2013	International Research Publication: A study of applying Vietnamese voice interaction for a context-aware aviation search engine; Authors: Quan Tran Lam, Hung Phan Dang; Poster paper of the 10 <sup>th</sup> IEEE RIVF International Conference on Computing and Communication Technologies (RIVF-2013); URL: <a href="http://uet.vnu.edu.vn/rivf2013/">http://uet.vnu.edu.vn/rivf2013/</a>
03/2013	International Research Publication: The VHO Project: A Semantic Solution for Vietnamese History Search System; Authors: Dang-Hung PHAN and Tuan-Dung CAO; Full paper of the 5 <sup>th</sup> Asian Conference on Intelligent Information and Database System (ACIIDS-2013) International Conference; URL: <a href="http://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007%2F978-3-642-36546-1_32">http://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007%2F978-3-642-36546-1_32</a> .
11/2012	<b>National award:</b> Take part in the SYCO group to build ViNAS system, achieve the second prize for potential software of Vietnam Talent Award season 2012.
06/2012	<b>Bachelor thesis:</b> Complete the Bachelor thesis with very good degree at HUST.
2012	<b>Scholarship</b> to encourage academic at school in the 2011-2012 school year for students with good academic at the HUST
2011	<b>Scholarship</b> to encourage academic at school in the 2010-2011 school year for students with good academic at the HUST.
2010	<b>Certificate of merit</b> of the HUST for students who join the "Support for the Exam Season" campaign in season 2010
2010	<b>Scholarship</b> to encourage academic at school in the 2009-2010 school year for students with good academic at the HUST
2009	Certificates of merit of HUST for students who positively take part in youth volunteers campaigns at the SOICT in the 2008-2009 school year
2009	<b>Scholarship</b> to encourage academic at school in the 2008-2009 school year for students with good academic at the HUST.
2008	<b>Scholarship</b> to encourage academic at school in the 2007-2008 school year for students with good academic at the HUST.

### 10. BEHAVIOURS

- Friendly, sociable.
- Creative.
- Responsibilities.

### 11. ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Team work.
- Communicate.
- Creativity.
- Time management.Overview, planning, problem analysis for the project.
- Organization and personnel management for the project.